Nanduri Venkata Phani Sai Anirudh (10267425) 
Class of 2026         
 
 
EDUCATION 
MBA BITS School of Management (BITSoM), Mumbai 2026 Pursuing First Rank 
B. E. (Mechanical Engineering) PSG College of Technology, Coimbatore 2018 7.87/10 1st Class 
Higher Secondary Certificate Exam Sri Chaitanya Junior College, Hyderabad 2014 84.3% A Grade 
Senior Secondary Examination Sri Chaitanya Techno School, Hyderabad 2012 8.8/10  
 
WORK EXPERIENCE 
Accenture Solutions Pvt Ltd: Specialist Data Scientist                                                                 (MayÆ22-MayÆ24) 
Key 
Achievements 
ò Recognized as Accenture Top Data Scientist, recognizing my performance among the top 20% globally 
ò Received total of 11 awards and recognitions such as the coveted STAR award and IS Elite Advocate 
Product 
Recommendation 
Engine 
ò Owned development of recommender algorithm that reduced product selection time of users by ~65% 
ò Built a high accuracy (~90%) ML model to predict switch user count for power savings, aiding ESG goals 
ò Developed an AI-chatbot to enable faster product recommendation (~85%), streamlining user experience 
ò Boosted new product adoption by ~20% by creating a risk framework using warranty, vulnerability, etc. 
ò Converted 4+ PoCs into ~$0.4M project by leading and developing them after securing VP endorsement 
ò Collaborated with design & engineering teams to ensure the final product met the predetermined criteria 
Counterfeit 
Detection 
ò Led development of AI-ML model to predict counterfeits, preventing business loss worth ~$1+ billion 
ò Developed rules engine to reduce time taken by expert team to identify counterfeit products by ~90% 
BRIDGEi2i Analytics Solutions Pvt Ltd (Acquired by Accenture): Senior Analytics Consultant (JunÆ18-AprÆ22) 
Key 
Achievements 
ò Recognized as an Ai2i icon for competence in AI/ML skills and excellence in capability development 
ò Received a total of 9 awards and recognitions such as the coveted SPOT, Team, & Torch Bearer award 
ò Trained a total of ~450+ individuals in 4 years on various technologies such as AI/ML, Excel, and SQL 
Pioneer Analytics 
Capability 
Development 
ò Led a 3-member team to deliver 3 dashboards, saving an estimated ~$0.25M per year on manpower 
ò Created a revenue model to forecast group wise revenue based on business inputs with ~95% accuracy 
ò Prevented ~$1.5M target miss by developing a monitoring dashboard using forecasts & sales behaviour 
ò Improved client performance (~25%) through insights from lead funnel, campaigns performance, etc.  
ò Mentored three college freshers to autonomously create dashboards and conduct client specific analysis 
Sales Target 
Estimation 
ò Analyzed product life cycle for realized revenue prediction, reducing the revenue target gap by ~30% 
ò Developed a VBA tool using life cycle curves, reducing ~95% manpower for supporting the tool usage 
Investment 
Optimizer 
ò Developed B2B budget optimization and simulation algorithms, integral to a marketing optimizer tool 
ò Boosted marketing profits by ~6% and halved decision-making time for a Fortune 500 B2B client 
ò Partnered with engineering, design, and QA teams to ensure proper functioning of tool and algorithm 
Market Mix 
Modelling 
ò Collaborated with 3 cross-functional counterparts to build a model and presented insights to leadership 
ò Insights contributed to justify marketing spend of $20M+ by showing marketing contribution of sales 
Spend & Tourism 
Analysis 
ò Conducted market research on SG&A spend by analyzing Fortune 500 companiesÆ financial statements 
ò Persuaded stakeholders to improve the system of estimating tourist spends by presenting a system analysis 
 
SUMMER INTERNSHIP 
Galderma India Pvt Ltd. û Business Analytics Intern                                                                      (AprÆ25-MayÆ25) 
Commercial 
Excellence 
ò Accelerated secondary sales validation by 4û5x by automating ERP data extraction with SKU mapping 
ò Analyzed 847-distributor survey to identify inconsistencies, driving standardization across regions 
ò Built in-house consolidation process, reducing vendor reliance and strengthening data governance 
 
POSITIONS OF RESPONSIBILITY 
Vice President 
Clubs (BITSoM) 
ò Elected to Student Council by 316 peers; steered governance and strategy for all 17 clubs 
ò Led 261 students across these clubs, driving collaboration & continuity in campus initiatives 
ò Created SOPs for event planning & execution, institutionalizing processes for future councils 
ò Streamlined recruitment of 148 applicants across clubs by designing a transparent process 
2025-2026 
POSH Committee 
(BITSoM) 
ò Served as ICC (POSH) member, contributing to complaint handling and ensuring compliance  
ò Worked with faculty/admin to ensure fair, confidential resolution aligned with campus policy 
2025-2026 
SCaLa Lead 
(BRIDGEi2i) 
ò Led Excel training and test program of the company end-to-end, training 180+ individuals 
ò Headed SQL training and test program of the company end-to-end, training 90+ individuals 
2020-2022 
2021-2022 
Global LeadersÆ 
Forum 
ò Led YLGC MUN for 3 years in various capacities by selecting judges & getting participants 
ò Organized TEDx by finalizing speakers, managing logistics, & overseeing the team 
2015-2018 
 
 
TECHNICAL SKILLS 
Python SQL ML AI Excel Tableau LLM 
 
CERTIFICATIONS 
ôGenAI with LLMsö by DeepLearning.Ai ôDS Core IIIö by Workera ôData Science Specializationö by IBM 
 

